ticketspice.com 2018-08-26

# Privacy Policy -

### Privacy Policy (Updated 5/2018)

Please note, the following privacy policy is purposed for clients and prospective clients of Webconnex products including RegFox, TicketSpice, GivingFuel, RedPodium and GroupRev, and all related web sites, downloadable software, mobile applications (including tablet applications), and other services provided by us and on which a link to this Privacy Policy is displayed, and all other communications with individuals through from written or oral means, such as email or phone). If you are an event goer or a donor, you are subject to the terms of use and privacy policy of the individual organization utilizing Webconnex software.

Webconnex LLC is the maker of RegFox, TicketSpice, GivingFuel, RedPodium and GroupRev.

Webconnex respects your privacy and works hard to safeguard the privacy of your personal data as you have provided it. We realize that the rapid growth of the Internet and online services raises questions concerning the nature, use and confidentiality of information collected about consumers. We want you to know that we apply our commitment to safeguarding privacy to our online and Internet activities.

### Definitions:

  * “Client” means a customer of Webconnex.
  * “Client Data“ means personal data, reports, addresses, and other files, folders or documents in electronic form that a User of the Service stores within the Service.
  * “Customer” means an individual other than a User, who uses the public area, to submit personal information and other details to the “Client”.
  * “Personal Data” means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person.
  * “Public Area” means the area of the Site that can be accessed both by Users and Visitors, without needing to log in.
  * “Restricted Area” means the area of the Site that can be accessed only by Users, and where access requires logging in.
  * “User” means an employee, agent, or representative of a Client, who primarily uses the restricted areas of the Site for the purpose of accessing the Service in such capacity.
  * “Visitor” means an individual other than a User, who uses the public area, but has no access to the restricted areas of the Site or Service.

### Personally Identifiable Information

Webconnex provides “Clients” with web based software that collects payment details and visitor information from its customers and participants. In order to process online payments and provide service to the customer, Webconnex asks for personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, city, state/province, zip/postal code) from you in order to complete the transaction, registration or payment. Webconnex only discloses personally-identifiable information to the Client in accordance to the Clients requirements. Webconnex does not share any information with unaffiliated companies or organizations. Because data submitted through Webconnex is a critical part of our business, it would be treated like our other assets in the context of a merger, sale or other corporate reorganization or legal proceeding.

### How We Use Information

#### On the client’s behalf

Webconnex uses the personally-identifiable information we collect online principally to provide the Visitor with the service(s) of registering for an event online, making an online donation, subscribing to a newsletter or otherwise registering for an online form on behalf of the Client. Postal and email address information, for example, enables communication about services/items offered and ordered, as well as the proper provisioning and billing of those services (email sales receipts, for example). Webconnex may involve other companies or vendors to carry out certain functions in marketing and delivering services to you (such as processing data files and sending the Visitor new order fulfillment information), and so may share data with those vendors to the extent necessary for them to perform their work. Of course, such partners and vendors must use that personally-identifiable information only for the purpose(s) for which it was shared and protect it from any further use.

#### Legal

We also provide personally-identifiable online information in response to subpoenas and other legal demands, and where we believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against individuals who may be endangering public safety or interfering with Webconnex property or services, or with our clients’ or others’ use of them.

#### Communications

Webconnex may use email addresses of Clients’ who signed up online to send an email related to our products and if affirmatively indicated a desire to receive additional information. If at any time, you would prefer not to receive further email communications at that email address, please contact Customer Support through the number or email address listed below.

For questions regarding this policy, contact:

Webconnex Customer Service  
455 Capitol Mall Suite 604  
Sacramento, CA 95814  
888-317-4539  
support@webconnex.com

#### Operations

We use the information – other than Client Data – to operate, maintain, enhance and provide all features of the Service; to provide the services and information that you request, to respond to comments and questions and to provide support to users of the Service. We process Client Data solely in accordance with the directions provided by the applicable Client or User.

#### Improvements

We use the information to understand and analyze the usage trends and preferences of our Visitors and Users, to improve the Service, and to develop new products, services, feature, and functionality. Should this purpose require Webconnex to process Client Data, then the data will only be used in anonymized or aggregated form.

### How We Collect Information

We collect different types of information from or through the Service. The legal bases for Webconnex’s processing of personal data are primarily that the processing is necessary for providing the Service in accordance with Webconnex’s Terms of Service and that the processing is carried out in Webconnex’s legitimate interests, which are further explained in the section “How We Use the Information We Collect” of this Policy. We may also process data upon your consent, asking for it as appropriate.

Webconnex collects information principally online upon signup of Webconnex as a Client and any registration form through any of the Webconnex products created by the Client. For example, when you order a product, take a survey, make a donation, to submit to contest, or other promotion from our Client, we capture this information on behalf of our Client. A client’s name, address (postal and email) and telephone number are usually asked for in these cases. But we might request other information, based on the services involved from the requirements of our Client. We do not share, make data or personally identifiable information of participants of Client available to any third party for any reason.

#### “Automatically Collected” Information

When a User or Visitor engages in the Service, we may automatically record certain information from the User’s or Visitor’s device by using various types of technology, including cookies, “clear gifs” or “web beacons.” This “automatically collected” information may include IP address or other device address or ID, web browser and/or device type, the web pages or sites visited just before or just after using the Service, the pages or other content the User or Visitor views or interacts with on the Service, and the dates and times of the visit, access, or use of the Service. We also may use these technologies to collect information regarding a Visitor or User’s interaction with email messages, such as whether the Visitor or User opens, clicks on, or forwards a message. This information is gathered from all Users and Visitors.

#### Information Collected by Clients

A Client or User may store or upload into the Service Client Data. Webconnex has no direct relationship with the individuals whose Personal Data it hosts as part of Client Data. Each Client is responsible for providing notice to its visitors and third persons concerning the purpose for which Client collects their Personal Data and how this Personal Data is processed in or through the Service as part of Client Data.

### Security

We use encryption, firewalls and other technology and security procedures to help protect the accuracy and security of your personal information and prevent unauthorized access or improper use. For example, you will note that while using some features of the Webconnex web site and online services, you may need to submit a password or some other type of authenticating information. All online sales procedures (for example member subscriptions or e-store purchases) are processed through our 256-bit SSL secure server.

### Your Choices

#### Access, Correction, Deletion

We respect your privacy rights and provide you with reasonable access to the Personal Data that you may have provided through your use of the Services. If you wish to access or amend any other Personal Data we hold about you, or to request that we delete or transfer any information about you that we have obtained from an Integrated Service, you may contact us as set forth in the “How to Contact Us” section. At your request, we will have any reference to you deleted or blocked in our database. You may also [fill out the form here](https://demo.regfox.com/gdpr-requests) to request actions for your personal information.

You may update, correct, or delete your Account information and preferences at any time by accessing your Account settings page on the Service. Please note that while any changes you make will be reflected in active user databases instantly or within a reasonable period of time, we may retain all information you submit for backups, archiving, prevention of fraud and abuse, analytics, satisfaction of legal obligations, or where we otherwise reasonably believe that we have a legitimate reason to do so.

You may decline to share certain Personal Data with us, in which case we may not be able to provide you with some of the features and functionality of the Service.

At any time, you may object to the processing of your Personal Data, on legitimate grounds, except if otherwise permitted by applicable law. If you believe your right to privacy granted by applicable data protection laws has been infringed upon, please contact Webconnex’s Data Protection Officer through the [privacy action request form](https://demo.regfox.com/gdpr-requests). You also have a right to lodge a complaint with data protection authorities.

This provision does not apply to Personal Data that is part of Client Data. In this case, the management of the Client Data is subject to the Client’s own Privacy Policy, and any request for access, correction or deletion should be made to the Client responsible for the uploading and storage of such data into the Service.

### Navigation Information

You may opt out from the collection of navigation information about your visit to the Site by Google Analytics by using the [Google Analytics Opt-out feature](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

### Opting out from Commercial Communications

If you receive commercial emails from us, you may unsubscribe at any time by following the instructions contained within the email or by sending an email to the address provided in the “How to Contact Us” section.

Users are able to view and modify settings relating to the nature and frequency of promotional communications that they receive from us by accessing the “Account Functionality” tab on the Service.

Please be aware that if you opt-out of receiving commercial email from us or otherwise modify the nature or frequency of promotional communications you receive from us, it may take up to ten (10) business days for us to process your request. Additionally, even after you opt-out from receiving commercial messages from us, you will continue to receive administrative messages from us regarding the Service.

Webconnex has no direct relationship with the Client’s customers or third party whose Personal Data it may process on behalf of a Client. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, delete inaccurate data or withdraw consent for further contact should direct his or her query to the Client or User they deal with directly. If the Client requests Webconnex to remove the data, we will respond to its request within thirty (30) days. We will delete, amend or block access to any Personal Data that we are storing only if we receive a written request to do so from the Client who is responsible for such Personal Data, unless we have a legal right to retain such Personal Data. We reserve the right to retain a copy of such data for archiving purposes, or to defend our rights in litigation. Any such request regarding Client Data should be addressed as indicated in the “How to Contact Us” section, and include sufficient information for Webconnex to identify the Client or its customer or third party and the information to delete or amend.

### Third-Party Services

The Service may contain features or links to web sites and services provided by third parties. Any information you provide on third-party sites or services is provided directly to the operators of such services and is subject to those operators’ policies, if any, governing privacy and security, even if accessed through the Service. We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of third-party sites or services to which links or access are provided through the Service. We encourage you to learn about third parties’ privacy and security policies before providing them with information.

### Minor and Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. Our Service is not directed to children under the age of 18, and we do not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 18 without obtaining parental consent. If you are under 18 years of age, then please do not use or access the Service at any time or in any manner. If we learn that Personal Data has been collected on the Service from persons under 18 years of age and without verifiable parental consent, then we will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. If you are a parent or guardian and discover that your child under 18 years of age has obtained an Account on the Service, then you may alert us at privacy@webconnex.com and request that we delete that child’s Personal Data from our systems.

The Service is not intended to be used by minors, and is not intended to be used to post content to share publicly or with friends. To the extent that a minor has posted such content on the Service, the minor has the right to have this content deleted or removed using the deletion or removal options detailed in this Privacy Policy. If you have any question regarding this topic, please contact us as indicated in the “How to Contact Us” section. Please be aware that, although we offer this deletion capability, the removal of content may not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of that content or information.

### Data Security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. We maintain appropriate administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect Personal Data against accidental or unlawful destruction, accidental loss, unauthorized alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access, misuse, and any other unlawful form of processing of the Personal Data in our possession. This includes, for example, firewalls, password protection and other access and authentication controls. We encrypt all data at rest as well as using SSL technology to encrypt data during transmission through public internet, and we also employ application-layer security features to further anonymize Personal Data.

However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or store on the Service, and you do so at your own risk. We also cannot guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. If you believe your Personal Data has been compromised, please contact us as set forth in the “How to Contact Us” section.

If we learn of a security systems breach, we will inform you and the authorities of the occurrence of the breach in accordance with applicable law.

### Data Controller and Data Processor

Webconnex does not own, control or direct the use of any of the Client Data stored or processed by a Client or User via the Service. Only the Client or Users are entitled to access, retrieve and direct the use of such Client Data. Webconnex is largely unaware of what Client Data is actually being stored or made available by a Client or User to the Service and does not directly access such Client Data except as authorized by the Client, or as necessary to provide Services to the Client and its Users.

Because Webconnex does not collect or determine the use of any Personal Data contained in the Client Data and because it does not determine the purposes for which such Personal Data is collected, the means of collecting such Personal Data, or the uses of such Personal Data, Webconnex is not acting in the capacity of data controller in terms of the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (Regulation (EU) 2016/679, hereinafter “GDPR”) and does not have the associated responsibilities under the GDPR. Webconnex should be considered only as a processor on behalf of its Clients and Users as to any Client Data containing Personal Data that is subject to the requirements of the GDPR. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, Webconnex does not independently cause Client Data containing Personal Data stored in connection with the Services to be transferred or otherwise made available to third parties, except to third party subcontractors who may process such data on behalf of Webconnex in connection with Webconnex’s provision of Services to Clients. Such actions are performed or authorized only by the applicable Client or User.

The Client or the User is the data controller under the Regulation for any Client Data containing Personal Data. Meaning that such party controls the manner such Personal Data is collected and used as well as the determination of the purposes and means of the processing of such Personal Data.

Webconnex is not responsible for the content of the Personal Data contained in the Client Data or other information stored on its servers (or its subcontractors’ servers) at the discretion of the Client or User, nor is Webconnex responsible for the manner in which the Client or User collects, handles disclosure, distributes or otherwise processes such information.

If you need a signed Data Processing Addendum in addition to the Terms of Service and Privacy Policy, you can find the document signed on behalf of [Webconnex here](https://demo.regfox.com/dpa).

### Changes and Updates to this Policy

Please revisit this page periodically to stay aware of any changes to this Policy, which we may update from time to time. If we modify the Policy, we will make it available through the Service, and indicate the date of the latest revision, and will comply with applicable law. Your continued use of the Service after the revised Policy has become effective indicates that you have read, understood and agreed to the current version of the Policy.

### How to Contact Us

Please contact us with any questions or comments about this Policy, your Personal Data, our use and disclosure practices, or your consent choices by email at privacy@webconnex.com. If you have any concerns or complaints about this Policy or your Personal Data, you may contact Webconnex’s Data Protection Officer by email at dpo@webconnex.com.

Updated: May 22, 2018
